Hello Hello
Привет Привет
How are you? I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky.
Как дела Я из города Хмельницкий Вы
How did
откуда
you understand it's cool? Listen, here's how it's correct: navel
Слушайте а у вас вот как правильно пупик
or navel poppik, through this you have a surname
или пупик поппик через это у вас фамилия
like that in Russia there is a Popov
такая это как вот в России есть Попов
surname only with the ending of the new priests in
фамилия только с окончанием нового
Ukraine,
Украине попы
I understood It's like For example, a blacksmith  there
я понял Это как Вот например кузнец там
Kuznetsov is the son of a blacksmith of folders It was the
Кузнецов это сын кузнеца папок Это был
son of a father a priest also the
сын папа священник также
intelligence of many Russians
интеллект многих русских
may be a joke
может быть шутку
No, you
Нет
still
еще
want to talk,
хотите поговорить
I don’t even know in reality Let’s
я не знаю даже на самом деле
try
Давайте попробуем
Damn that’s all Let’s have you been sitting for a long time
Блин так все Давайте а вы давно сидите
or like an hour and a half I’ve been sitting for an hour and a half
или как полтора часа полтора часа уже
and left before  before this,
сижу вышел а до этого до этого
I took it situationally Well, I didn’t go out every time,
ситуативно брал Ну я не каждый раз вышла
I realized
я понял
maybe you have some news
вот Может у вас какие-то новости есть
there, I don’t know the news in Kursk, the
там я не знаю новости в Курске аэродром
Halena airfield was hit by our military, it’s awesome That’s what
халена влупили военные наши офигенно
I haven’t heard
Вот этого я не слышал
anything about this,
ничего по этому поводу не могу потому
I can’t because I don’t  I heard
что я не слышал
something else, it seems like
Вот а еще чего-нибудь
this, it seems like
вот вроде как
Well, not everyone will agree with you, we will not
Ну не все с вами согласна будем нет
Everyone has a certain audience,
У каждого есть определенная аудитория
which is
которая вот
his Vector does not coincide with this audience for me
Вектор его мне не совпадает с этой
And if this is normal in
аудиторией А если это нормально в
society, they are different
обществе разные
Okay Listen, please answer
Хорошо Слушайте вот ответьте пожалуйста
you streams  are you leading or are you
вы стримы ведете или вы записываете
just recording streams I'm doing streams people are on
просто стримы веду стримы люди сейчас на
stream now people are watching
стриме то сейчас люди смотрят
Ukrainians guys Hello to all of you let's make
украинцы ребята Всем вам привет давайте
peace let's
мириться давайте давайте разговоры
talk talk let's talk now right now
разговаривать давайте сейчас вот сейчас
1 So attention we announce 1 reconciliation
1 Так внимание объявляем 1 примирение
chat roulette So let's what do we need
чат рулетки Так давайте что нам нужно
to make peace
чтобы помириться
at least stop first  combat
как минимум сначала прекратить боевое
action talk Super What is needed
действие разговаривать Супер Что нужно
to stop hostilities,
чтобы прекратить боевые действия вот
Russia has entered the territory of Ukraine and
Россия зашла на территорию Украины и
is fighting what is needed who should stop
воюет что нужно кто должен прекратить
hostilities
боевые действия
both sides yes, that is, I
обе стороны да то есть я так правильно
understand correctly that Russia should withdraw its
понимаю что Россия должна вывести свои
troops from the territory of Ukraine and not
войска за территорию Украины и не
shoot and Ukraine should not interfere  in Russia,
стрелять а Украина не лезть в России
too, don’t shoot like that.
тоже не стрелять так
I think that in general at this stage, even
Я думаю что вообще на данном этапе даже
where the troops are now,
где сейчас войска есть остановиться А
stop And then talk stop stop stop
дальше разговаривать стоп стоп стоп еще
again, wait, there’s something I can’t understand, that
раз подождите я что-то не могу понять то
is, Russia got in here,
есть Россия влезла сюда
she’s killing us and we have to stop
она нас убивает и мы должны остановиться
if she doesn’t  will leave our territory
если она не выйдет с нашей территории
to stop, everyone must
остановиться остановиться должны все
stop in Russia
остановка России
in order to be able to
для того чтобы нормально можно
talk normally. If you have
разговаривать нормально Если у вас горло
a knife in your throat, for example, but
нож например
your country has, yes, our country has
а у вас у страны есть да у нас у страны
a knife near the city, your troops on our
нож возле города ваши войска на нашей
territory are captured, cities of the
территории есть захвачены города
territory Yes, near
территории Да возле
But what  It’s stopping you from moving this Knife,
Но что вам мешает отодвинуть этот Нож
let’s say so, and continue to fight
скажем так и дальше продолжить воевать
if the politicians don’t agree,
если политики не договариваться
he flew to Sevastopol,
он в Севастополь прилетела
and you know what my
а знаете какое по этому поводу мое
opinion on this is interesting? Let’s say she’s very
мнение интересно Давайте она очень
sad then that’s how Well, at
грустное тогда вот как Ну по крайней
least for me because I’m the daughter of Ukrainians,
мере для меня потому что я украинцев
I’m interested Good good
мне интересно Хорошо хорошо
that all these retreats are
что вот эти все отступления именно на
actually a regrouping
самом деле перегруппировка
and are being done for what purpose, in order to
и делается для чего для того чтобы
exhaust the
извести
population of Ukraine to the maximum, precisely the
население Украины по максимуму именно то
population that can hold weapons
население которое может держать оружие
did not understand,
не понял
they fled from near Kiev Kharkov, why, in
убежали из под Киева Харькова для чего
order to regroup, create a line of
чтобы перегруппироваться создать линию
defense of this so-called
обороны вот это вот так называемого
Zaporozhye now  region, there is now a
Запорожской области сейчас находится
line of this very thing, as it is called,
линии этого самого как он называется
here is the line of the suriki for the fact that a lot is being lost
вот линия суровики на то что теряется
to retreat so that
много отступить вот чтобы потерялась
more of yours are lost. So
больше ваших Вот
you regrouped from the Kharkov
вы перегруппировались из Харьковской
region so that we could
области для того чтобы мы могли Белгород
fire at Belgorod this way it’s easier,
обстреливать так проще
these are collateral losses, unfortunately, it’s
это сопутствующие потери к сожалению
cool, not a single war would be without this
прикольно ни одна война без этого не
there are
происходит
border territories with countries
приграничные территории со странами
that Why didn’t they completely
которые Почему бы не до конца
regroup, for example, they tried to
перегруппировались например пробовали на
attack Kupyansk,
Купянск еще наступать
but I don’t know anything about it, you don’t
а я насчет этого ничего не знаю не
know Yes, it’s interesting,
знаете Да интересно
I heard that something had accumulated there,
Я слышал что там что-то накопилось пошли
how did the merchant
Как правильно купецк
turn out correctly or did you need to regroup everyone? It
получается или ваши нужно было всех
seems to me  that
Мне кажется что да
yes Well, you don’t think it’s not possible to put forward
Ну вы не см-то не выставлять
reconciliation,
по примирении
but do you think it’s somehow to move the
а вы думаете Это как-то двигать
negotiations? Yes, I
переговорам
doubt it.
сомневаюсь
But the more aggression, the less
Но чем больше агрессии тем меньше
desire to negotiate, I
желание идти на переговоры
understand. Well,
понял
no, wait, let’s be honest, yes,
Ну нет подождите вот Давайте по-честному
the level of aggression from Russia decreased for the sake of
уровень агрессии от России снижался ради
negotiations  it was descending, for example,
переговоров снижался было такое например
as it was descending, for example,
как он снижался
in Istanbul, negotiations
он например в Стамбуле переговоры
with drones
беспилотниками
earlier
раньше
because it appeared well for you
потому что у вас это появилось
after the 100
хорошо после 100
negotiation area
переговоровской области
[music]
[музыка]
after negotiations. What did they agree on
после переговоров А что там договорились
about turning around the fighting
о том чтобы перекрутить боевые действия
and negotiating? I hope you don’t mind,
И договариваться Я надеюсь вы не против
I’ll take a cigarette  and I’ll smoke I don’t understand, it turns
я возьму сигаретку и покурю Я не понял
out that Russia said In these What to
то получается Россия сказала В эти О чем
talk about to Istanbul that Russia will take
говорить Стамбуле что Россия заберет
its troops from near Kiev and what Ukraine
свои войска из-под Киева а Украина что
should have done
должна была сделать
is that it will talk further they
то что будет разговаривать дальше
agreed there that Russia is
договорились там были что Россия
taking away troops and they talk further Yes
забирает войска и говорят дальше Да
no there was a conversation like that  that Russia
нет был разговор Такой что Россия
is withdrawing its troops from the Kiev
отводит свои войска из Киевской из
region from the Chernigov region
Черниговской области
is going to negotiate
собирается договариваться
in Istanbul it was
в Стамбуле договаривались о том что
agreed that Russia is withdrawing its
договорились о том что Россия отводит
troops and Ukraine will be ready to
войска и Украина будет готова
negotiate they
переговоров
defused the situation wait in Istanbul there were
разрядили ситуацию подожди Стамбуле были
negotiations
переговоры
there were in Istanbul I just can’t
были были Стамбуле Я просто не могу
understand
понять
the situation I understood correctly that
ситуацию Я правильно понял что в
there were negotiations in Istanbul Ukraine Russia
Стамбуле были переговоры Украина Россия
came to negotiations in Istanbul and
приехала на переговоры в Стамбул и
agreed that Russia would withdraw its
договорились что Россия уводит свои
troops from near Kiev and Ukraine would
войска из-под Киева а Украина будет
negotiate nothing, I didn’t understand in short Okay
делать переговоры нифига не понял короче
okay, if you don’t like it, I’ll tell you
Хорошо ладно как вы не любите я вам
a gesture of goodwill, the so-called that we are
жест доброй воли так называемый что мы
ready for
готовы переговорам
full-fledged negotiations  we are withdrawing troops from Kiev,
полноценным мы отводим войска от Киева
you were in the mood for a conversation,
вы были настроены на разговор
no one was in the mood
никто не настроился
because your positions had already been occupied there
потому что там уже заняли позиции ваши
because they were already there. Like at the very beginning
потому что туда уже Как Вот самом начале
in the first days, it was no longer possible to go there
в первые дни уже было не зайти потому
because they were already digging in there.
что там уже копались
Listen, tell me what they write to your aunt.
Слушайте а скажите что у вас тёте пишут
I don’t  I know
Я не знаю
I’m not distracted at the beginning of the time
я не отвлекаюсь начатое время
you Read I want it
вы Прочтите Я хочу вот
now I think I’m sure there will be motiki
сейчас я думаю уверен что будет мотики
now Yes I’m sure to go vin
сейчас Да я по-любому уверен идти вин
idiot there anyway Here’s something like that Why
[__] там Вот что-нибудь такое А чего
so where did you say that yourself
так Вы откуда сами так
writes It’s a pity that after the summer you can give it to
пишет Жаль что через летний можно дать в
face
морду
Andrey grips popcorn so cap writes
Андрей хваты попкорн так шапочку пишет
that you Alexander is important 28 years old
что ты Александр важен 28 лет 30
September 30, 94, the year you were born Yes,
этого сентября 94 года рождения тебя Да
Oksana Bazheno’s wife is 28 years old
жена у Оксана бажено 28 лет 19
February 19, 1995
февраля 1995 года
Roshevskaya creature
[__] рошевская
2 more 3G border here comments are just
еще 2 3G граница тут комменты просто
awesome I read where the storyteller
офигенно Я же зачитал куда сказочник
Dreamer writes that he’s a dork
Фантазер пишут что долбодятел
so he is no more than 14 years old, so he sent him to
так ему не больше 14 лет так отправил
learn the right to trace history on the lips
учить право историю по губам проводить
if you are so good at making these gestures, let him
если у вас так хорошо выходит эти жесты
do it from all over Ukraine,
делать Пусть делает же со всей Украины
let’s sit down and talk. By the way,
сядем поговорим Да кстати
very smart people write,
очень умные люди пишут
look, if you are so good at
смотри если у вас так получается хорошо
making goodwill gestures, then
проводить жесты доброй воли да то
do more from all over Ukraine with this we’ll
делайте еще же со всей Украины с этим
talk so writes the victim cleaning up the abortion
поговорим так пишет жертва уборка аборта
by slurping good luck then Sharikova
по хлебал удачи потом Шарикова
so
так
similar to Khovansky looks like 40
на Хованского схожий выглядит на 40
argues at 12 Andrey FSB is resting
рассуждает на 12 Андрей ФСБ отдыхает
lovers of moral humiliation still read then
любители моральных унижений еще читать
read If you want
то читайте Если хотите
Let’s throw in some more
Давайте подкиньте еще эпитета всяких
interesting epithet Let’s have a competition for  the most
интересно Давайте конкурс на самый
awesome epithet for this orc is the pig breeders.
офигенный эпитет этому орку свиноводцы
In short, when they write to me about this while Let's
Короче когда мне ворку вот этого пока
talk to you shadows
пишут Давайте с вами поговорим тени
now I'm already reading survival cuckold
сейчас я уже выживание читаю куколд
herring [ __ ]
селедку
meter his seller in Yekaterinburg
сраный метр его продавец Екатеринбурге
so send for Russian ships dad
так послать за российские корабли батя
didn't wipe it on time and you birch snot
не вытер вовремя и тебя березы сопля
red broth face [ __ ] my damn
рыжая бульонная рожа нахер блин мой
comment Read
комент Зачитай
sucker give him herrings to the beach He
[__] дайте ему селедки на пляж Он
supports an
поддерживает
example of Russian cretinism he writes the Cossacks
образец русского кретинизма пишет казаки
respond to the Russian orc The cat is trash
отвечают русскому орку Кошак помойный
so boldur near Kiev they got stars
так болдур под Киевом получили звезды
Sharikov's son
сын Шарикова
also Gerasimov to the front strategy in
также Герасимов на фронт стратегия в
the chat writes True boy in panties
чате пишет Правда мальчик в трусиках Да
Well, let's run further read to you for
ну что побежим дальше начитали тебе на
sleep  the coming one will be good
сон грядущий будет хорошо
I love these so much Let's agree to
Я так люблю эти Давайте договариваться
put up with bullshit-miruns a
мириться бляха-мируны
kilogram right at a time autumn and the butt is
килограмм прям за раз осень а попок
even more and more important YouTube is driving us
дуже и дуже важен YouTube загоняя нас
through the quarries into a shadow ban and even then the
через карьерки в теневый бан и дуже то
video is not shown to people,
видео не показывается людям часто
information about streams is often shown in
показывается информация про стримы для
order for the little operational animal
того чтобы мало оперативный зверёк
subscribe and right at once and the butt is there in a
подпишись а прям за раз а попок там в
kilogram, we'll cover the video
килограмме окрим видео
information and we are with you
информация и мы с вами
[music]
[музыка]